Well, your father needs to get going.
Be good kids and listen to your big sister.
--Where are you going?
--Don't leave!
--Bring me something!
--I wanna go, too!
--No fair!
--Let me come with you!
--Pretty please!
Sorry. I'm afraid not this time.
--Huh? How come?
--It's not fair!
Behave, you guys! Don't be selfish!
You're making it hard for him!
Fine... Make sure all the kids get along.
Yup! Good luck with your work!
Thanks. I think it's time I head out.
--Take care!
--Bring me something!
Darling...
I'm sorry. Take care of the kids.
Let's go.
I suppose if I'm attacked,
it'll be during the speech?
I can't say for sure,
but that seems the most likely.
Only then will most of our brass
be gathered in one spot.
However, it's protocol to make escape
plans at the last moment for security.
Naturally, VIPs will use carriages.
Let's sit them at the
"special seats" on the edge.
Clump them together as much as possible.
Are you sure about this?
Compared to our predecessors,
the Tyburs haven't been playing around.
We've been building relations
with the world's elite,
improving the reputation of Eldians,
and watching Paradis Island's movements.
But we should've been watching
our own backyard.
Before we knew it, we had enemies
crossing the sea and at our necks.
At this point, they might get
sliced at any moment.
It's the conspirators working with
Paradis who I fear most.
We still don't know who they are.
As you know, our motherland
Marley has many enemies.
Some, in our own military.
We'll smoke them out
by lighting a fire under their asses.
We can plan for their attack
and use it to our advantage.
Unless you have a better idea,
we proceed as planned.
Even if they take the bait,
we lose way too much.
We'll sacrifice incompetent officers.
If the enemy's goal is to damage
Marley's military, it works perfectly.
When you rebuild the military, the party
will approve whomever you choose.
But so many will die.
Most of them will be Eldians!
They're spawn of the devil!
Don't change on me now, Commander Magath.
You've sent countless Eldians marching
into machine guns and land mines.
Why does it matter whether
they wear uniforms or not?
Just keep doing what you've always done.
Let me say one thing:
This isn't war. We don't know the enemy,
their goal, or how they'll attack.
Plus, the venue will be packed
with a huge crowd.
Lord Tybur, I doubt I'll be able to protect you.
If we proceed, you will die.
They won't pass you up as bait.
Of course. I'm prepared for that.
Unless I stand on stage,
the world will not take notice.
The military, newspapers, and
ambassadors won't gather in one place.
Above all, the Eldians of the internment
zone and I must be made tragic victims.
Victims of an "unforeseen attack."
If I am the sole survivor,
the world will not become our ally.
There's no doubt that Eldians
are spawn of the devil.
And there's no doubt
that we are devils ourselves.
"The War Hammer Titan"
Get up, Gabi! Udo!
Stand up! Hurry!
Zofia?
--Zofia!
--Udo, don't!
--Udo, get back!
Hurry! We gotta lift this!
Udo!
Brother... You fulfilled the
Tyburs' duty admirably.
Commander! The War Hammer is getting wrecked!
Commander! The Warriors are missing!
--General Calvi and the brass are dead!
--We should check for survivors!
--It's dangerous here!
--We need orders!
Commander!
Commander?
It's a useless plink, but this signals
the beginning of Marley's counterattack.
To think they'd make such a grand entrance.
What's more, it looks to be the usurper
of the Founding Titan--the Attack Titan.
Eren Jaeger has come in person!
Saves us a trip to the island.
Get in position! Prepare for battle!
Yes, sir!
Hey, what's all the ruckus about?
What are you doing?! We have to get out--
Remember it, people.
I'm the one who took the first shot.
Shit! What the hell?! It's a battlefield now!
Colt! How's Udo?!
Not good. He needs the hospital.
Udo! You're kidding!
Shit! Falco! Where are you?!
What's happening out there?!
By these tremors, I'd guess Titans are fighting.
Are you serious?!
Us being trapped down here
is answer enough.
We've gotta get out somehow.
How?
What the hell?
You're late!
--Pieck!
--You okay?!
Throw us a rope!
Got it!
The Panzer Unit? How'd they know?
I told 'em to follow since Beardy was shady.
Back then?
This soldier seems shady. Follow behind us.
A Titan attacked during the speech!
For real?!
The War Hammer is fending it off!
Where's the Cart's gear?
At HQ! We'll have it done in 15!
Make it 10!
Roger!
I'm going ahead.
Wait, Porco. Before you rush in...
What the--?!
You're kidding... There's no way!
--Yeah, it hit!
--Anti-Titan artillery packs a punch!
--Reload!
--Commander Magath,
let's finish off Eren Jaeger!
Without the Founding Titan, they're doomed!
--No.
--Huh?
Killing the Founding Titan
only postpones the problem.
We need to have the War Hammer eat it!
We're here to ensure that happens!
B-But, Commander...
I don't think the War Hammer
is trying to eat it.
The War Hammer's a monster!
It beat the Attack Titan!
The War Hammer wins!
So that's Eren Jaeger, huh?
It's really gonna finish him off!
Usurper, Eren Jaeger.
Do you have any last words?
Now or never, Mikasa.
You guys actually came.
Eren, please...
Come home.
"The War Hammer Titan is encased in a shell
created by its extraordinary hardening abilty.
It can use that same hardening ability to
construct any weapon it envisions at will."
With the chain of command broken,
our military will be put to the test!
Call down all our troops doing
special training in the mountains!
Bring the fleet, too! Converge on top
of 'em with 30,000 soldiers!
I want Liberio surrounded!
Don't let the Founding Titan
or a single island devil escape!
Have fun while it lasts.
There's no future for you now.
With this massacre, you just ensured
every major nation gets involved now.
The world will see the Eldian Empire
as a threat, just like Willy planned.
Now, no one's gonna let you live.
But even they must've
known that going into this.
Which means...
You damn devils!
Shoot 'em down!
Those morons!
Hey! You gonna burn the whole zone down?!
What part of keeping civilian casualties
to a minimum don't you get, Floch?!
The only thing here are enemies
and places they live!
Did you forget how they massacred
humanity inside the walls?!
We were eaten alive, dammit!
They've got it coming!
You're still saying that?
Look. Eren's telling us something--to fight!
We shouldn't just wait
for our deaths in the walls.
What we need... is a devil like him!
Eren... Do you have any idea what you've done?
You killed civilians.
You killed children, too.
You've done things that can't be undone.
Mikasa, it's not over yet.
Impossible! I blew away its nape!
And I crushed it with all my strength.
Yet, it's not dead.
I see...
The War Hammer Titan... It uses
hardening to make whatever it needs.
That must be why it won't die,
no matter what we do.
Mikasa, get its attention.
If this works, I can eat the War Hammer.
Sorry, we're at full capacity!
And the kid's dead already!
Come on! At least look at him!
Aren't you a candidate? Take a look around you!
We need you, doc!
Okay, I'm coming!
Gabi, stay with your family.
I'm not sure if anywhere's safe.
Get as far from the plaza as possible.
I'm gonna look for Falco and--
I'm going, too.
Because I don't understand
why Udo and Zofia had to die.
Wait, Gabi! Don't!
Hey, stop! You're headed towards a war zone!
Gabi!
What are you doing here?!
Mr. Gate Guard! I'll fight, so let me through!
Don't be an idiot, brat!
You head back home and...
--What the--?!
--Enemy attack?!
From where?!
--They're above!
--Shit!
Go on, Gabi! Run!
Hey, are you--?
Mister...
This side's blocked off. Let's go, Sasha.
Conny... Did you forget about the lights?
Oh, right.
Jean, we stalled the reinforcements.
And the lights?
They're all in place.
Are things going well?
For the time being.
As long as we take that thing out in time.
But who knows?
Anything can happen at this point.
What's to come when this battle is over?
For us to know, we have to survive.
I knew something felt off to me.
It didn't seem right how
the War Hammer appeared.
And that's because its body
formed from the feet up.
Not from its nape, but from
underneath the stage.
Which means its body is...
Shoot! The War Hammer
is about to get eaten!
I've been waiting for this moment!
I'm retaking the Founding Titan!
Eren!
What?! I can't bite?!
Was that him?! Is that... Ackermann?!
This ain't looking good!
You're kidding! Can't you see I'm a Titan?!
These guys are just humans,
yet they're coming to kill me?!
These guys... They're the devils of Paradis!
The devils of Paradis.
The Warriors take a stand against
soldiers who soar through the air.
Will Gabi and Falco's cries reach Reiner?
Next episode: "Assault."